Guide to the Joseph W. Reed and George Creeger Collection of Human Likenesses, 1840 - 1900
Joseph W. Reed and George Creeger Collection of Human Likenesses 1840-1900
- Series XII. Photograph album
  - Photograph Album1858-1890 (Box 7, Photoalbum 1)
    [Page 1] Raffael Moini Suook, circa 1860-1875 Child seated on fringed ottoman
    Wm. Klauser Parterre Gallery, circa 1865-1870 Woman standing, full length portrait
    [Page 2] Charles Fredericks NY, circa 1860-1865 Man, head and shoulders portrait
    Brady, circa 1865-1875 Woman seated, wearing overblouse with pleated trim
    [Page 3] Young woman, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1860-1865
    Fredericks, circa 1860-1865 Man standing, holding top hat, three-quarters length portrait
    [Page 4] Bogardus, New York, circa 1860-1865 Lilly Spofford
    Man standing, holding top hat at side, full length portrait, circa 1865-1875 Small notation at right of photograph: 20048
    [Page 5] Man, head and shoulders portrait in three-quarters view, 1875-1885
    Woman, head and shoulders portrait in three-quarters view, circa 1875-1885 Apparently a copy of a photographic image
    [Page 6] Man standing, left hand resting on balustrade, circa 1875-1885
    Woman, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 7] Sarony, circa 1875-1885 Woman, leaning forward on carved support covered with a textile
    Man, head and shoulders portrait, near profile, circa 1860-1870
    [Page 8] Woman standing, full length portrait, circa 1870-1885
    [Page 9] Disderi, circa 1865-1873 Napoleon III
    Young woman, portrait in three-quarters view, tinted hair ornament and earring Raised oval mount, circa 1870-1880
    [Page 10] Boy standing, leaning on chair arm, circa 1860-1875
    Woman seated, right hand resting on left forearm Tintype, circa 1870-1880
    [Page 11] Woman wearing necklace with crucifix, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1870-1880
    Man with textile draped around shoulders, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1860-1870
    [Page 12] Brady, circa 1880-1890 Girl standing at table, table covered with textile, frame and book on table
    Girl with ringlets seated, with feet on cane seat Tinted tintype, circa 1870-1880
    [Page 13] Brady, circa 1870-1880 Man standing, holding top hat
    Woman, seated, three-quarters view, circa 1865-1875
    [Page 14] Man with moustache, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1860-1870
    Woman, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1860-1870
    [Page 15] Disderi, circa 1865-1878 King Victor Emmanuel I
    Man, full length portrait, circa 1870-1880
    [Page 16] Disderi, circa 1860-1870 Clotildi
    Child standing with hands on chair seat, circa 1860-1870
    [Page 17] Disderi, circa 1858-1862 Prince Imperial
    Woman standing, right hand on chairback, full length portrait in three quarters view circa 1865-1875
    [Page 18] Child standing on chair seat with hand on covered table, circa 1860-1870 Tinted
    Woman, ribbon tied at neck, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 19] Brady Woman standing, hands together and lifted, circa 1865-1875
    Brady J.G. Bennett, circa 1865-1875
    [Page 20] Two young women, one seated on balustrade, the other standing, both wearing dress of the same cut and trim, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 21] Man standing, holding top hat at hip, right forearm resting on covered support circa 1860-1870
    Man seated at writing table, leaning on elbow with right hand against side of face circa 1870-1880
    [Page 22] Woman, head and shoulders portrait, near profile, circa 1860-1865
    Man with muttonchops, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 23] Man, white cravat, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1870-1890
    Woman seated, wearing light cape and dark bonnet, circa 1870-1890
    [Page 24] Young woman seated, long hair loose, circa 1870-1880
    Man with beard, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1860-1870
    [Page 25] Brady, circa 1860-1870 Woman standing, left elbow resting on mantelpiece with finger at her chin
    Brady, circa 1870-1880 Man standing with left hand resting on chair back
    [Page 26] Man with beard, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 27] Man with beard, handkerchief in jacket pocket, head and shoulders portrait circa 1860-1870
    Woman seated, left arm resting on book on covered table, circa 1865-1875
    [Page 28] Girl seated on chair, tinted Raised oval mount, circa 1870-1880
    Boy seated on covered table Raised oval mount, circa 1870-1880
    [Page 29] Street scene with two Asian men and Caucasian man seated in litter, circa 1865-1875
    Man with beard, head and shoulders portrait in three quarters view, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 30] Man, head and shoulders portrait in three quarters view, circa 1875-1885
    Sarony Woman seated, arms crossed on top of chair back, circa 1865-1875
    [Page 31] Woman with elaborate hairdo, head and shoulders portrait in near profile circa 1860-1870
    Man standing, holding cane and right hand tucked in vest, full length portrait circa 1870-1880
    [Page 32] Man, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1870-1880
    Woman with pin at collar, head and neck portrait, circa 1860-1870
    [Page 33] Woman wearing velvet ribbon necklace with pendant, seated Raised oval mount, circa 1870-1880
    Woman wearing earrings and pin, head and shoulders portrait, circa 1860-1870
    [Page 34] Man standing, wearing military uniform, full length portrait, circa 1860-1870
    Woman with ruffled collars, head and shoulders portrait Apparently a copy of a photographic image, circa 1870-1880
    [Page 35] Man seated, with left forearm on fringed armrest, circa 1890-1900
    Woman, with hair ornament, earrings and necklace, head and shoulders portrait circa 1860-1865
    [Page 36] Boy standing, leaning against podium, holding a cane, derby on podium, circa 1860-1870
    Woman, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view, circa 1860-1870
    [Page 37] Man, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view Raised oval mount, circa 1870-1880
    Woman, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view Raised oval mount, circa 1870-1880
    [Page 38] Man, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view, circa 1860-1865
    Girl, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view Tinted, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 39] Child seated on curtain-covered chair Tinted, circa 1870-1880
    Woman, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view Tinted, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 40] Durone & Murer Milan Garibaldi, 1861
    Mayer & Fierson Man seated in fringed chair, left forearm resting on covered table, circa 1860-1870
    [Page 41] Woman, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view Apparently a copy of a photographic image, circa 1870-1880
    Bogardi [?] S.F.B. Morse, seated, three quarters view, circa 1860-1870
    [Page 42] Priviligeo d’Invenzione Man standing with left forearm on chair back, circa 1870-1880
    Woman seated with elbow on table and hand at her face, circa 1870-1880
    [Page 43] Priviligeo d’Invenzione Girl, three quarters view, circa 1870-1880
    Priviligeo d’Invenzione Boy standing, wearing large jacket and watch chain at vest, circa 1870-1880
    [Page 44] Man, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view, circa 1860-1870
    Man with beard, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view, circa 1860-1870
    [Page 45] Broadhurst, Phila. Man in military uniform, cap in right hand, sabre at waist, full length, circa 1860-1865
    Two women, both in bonnets, one seated, one standing, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 46] Man, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view, circa 1860-1865
    Woman, ruffles and bow at neck, wearing a locket, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view, circa 1870-1880
    [Page 47] Man and woman, man standing, woman seated, circa 1860-1865
    Disderi st Cie Phot. [illeg]istori. Woman holding child, another child leaning into her, carried child’s head under woman’s shawl, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 48] Boy wearing derby hat, leaning against balustrade, full length portrait, circa 1860-1865
    Rockwood Photographer, 829 Broadway, NY Dr. Pierce, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 49] Woman wearing earrings, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view, circa 1860-1865
    Woman wearing hair ornament and pins at collars, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view, circa 1860-1865
    [Page 50] Young man standing, holding hat, circa 1870-1880
    Woman in hat, head and shoulders portrait, three quarters view, circa 1860-1865